{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4358","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4358","name":"Domino's Pizza","address":"7603 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Domino Pizza LLC","licenseNumber":"PS031422","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.12305,42.31286","geojson":{"id":"4358","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.12304687,42.31285858]},"properties":{"name":"Domino's Pizza","owner":"Domino Pizza LLC","address":"7603 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"PS031422","establishmentid":"4358","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"28/4/2021"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51623784","name":"La Casa Ice Cream ","address":"7615 W. Vernor Hwy","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"857","name":"Sherry Lee's Place","address":"7631 Vernor St.W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51623382","name":"Utila Juices","address":"7600 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"279","name":"Pauls Pizzeria","address":"7635 Vernor St. W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5007","name":"Famous Tasty Chicken","address":"7431  Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51623109","name":"Ice Cream & Cafe La Ni√±a","address":"7431 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3255","name":"West Vernor Subway","address":"7431 Vernor St.W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4873","name":"Neveria La Chilindrina","address":"7431 Vernor W","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3399","name":"Sweet Maria's","address":"7647 Vernor W. ","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"201","name":"Taqueria El Nacimiento","address":"7400 Vernor St.W.","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"57035","inspectionDate":"2021-12-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-209.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, EMPLOYEES shall properly store their PERSONAL CARE ITEMS.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Personal items","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"To prevent contamination of food or food related items","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Personal items","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"5-501.115","violationDescription":"A storage area and enclosure for REFUSE, recyclables, or returnables shall be maintained free of unnecessary items, and clean.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Refuse storage area(s)/enclosures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE","subLocation":"Dumpster(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Covered waste container","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALL(S)","subLocation":"Wall panels","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"56815","inspectionDate":"2021-12-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53807","inspectionDate":"2020-12-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Test strips","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Food thermometer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"5-501.115","violationDescription":"A storage area and enclosure for REFUSE, recyclables, or returnables shall be maintained free of unnecessary items, and clean.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Refuse storage area(s)/enclosures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE","subLocation":"Dumpster(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"Floor tiles","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"Thermometer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"48324","inspectionDate":"2019-07-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."}]},{"inspectionid":"42686","inspectionDate":"2018-06-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"8-304.11","violationDescription":"Upon acceptance of the PERMIT issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, the PERMIT HOLDER in order to retain the PERMIT shall:\n(A) Post the PERMIT in a location in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT that is conspicuous to CONSUMERS; \n(B) Comply with the provisions of this Code including the conditions of a granted VARIANCE as specified under ¬ß 8-103.12, and APPROVED plans as specified under ¬ß 8-201.12;\n(C) If a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT is required under ¬ß 8-201.13 to operate under a HACCP PLAN, comply with the plan as specified under ¬ß 8-103.12;\n(D) Immediately contact the REGULATORY AUTHORITY to report an illness of a FOOD EMPLOYEE or CONDITIONAL EMPLOYEE as specified under ¬∂ 2-201.11(B); \n(E) Immediately discontinue operations and notify the REGULATORY AUTHORITY if an IMMINENT HEALTH HAZARD may exist as specified under ¬ß 8-404.11;\n(F) Allow representatives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY access to the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT as specified under ¬ß 8-402.11;\n(G) Except as specified under ¬∂ (H) of this section, replace existing facilities and EQUIPMENT specified in ¬ß 8-101.10 with facilities and EQUIPMENT that comply with this Code if:\n(1) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement because the facilities and EQUIPMENT constitute a public health HAZARD or nuisance or no longer comply with the criteria upon which the facilities and EQUIPMENT were accepted,\n(2) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement of the facilities and EQUIPMENT because of a change of ownership, or\n(3) The facilities and EQUIPMENT are replaced in the normal course of operation;\n(H) Upgrade or replace refrigeration EQUIPMENT as specified under Subparagraph 3-501.16(A)(2)(b), if the circumstances specified under Subparagraphs (G)(1) - (3) of this section do not occur first, and 5 years pass after the REGULATORY AUTHORITY adopts this Code;\n(I) Comply with directives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY in regard to the PERMIT HOLDER'S FOOD ESTABLISHMENT or in response to community emergencies; \n(J) Accept notices issued and served by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY according to LAW; and \n(K) Be subject to the administrative, civil, injunctive, and criminal remedies authorized in LAW for failure to comply with this Code or a directive of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"38977","inspectionDate":"2017-05-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¬∂ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¬∂ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¬∂ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"37639","inspectionDate":"2016-10-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4358"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}